{
    "id": "dca71b9b5d834d11835c7063db10abb6",
    "title": "Negative structures – grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "4cffabb2f7024cd1a7db33626d5e12c9",
            "title": "Negative Structures",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………….. – I will look after you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Not worry",
                        "Worry not",
                        "Don't worry"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I liked the salad but I ………………….. the soup.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't like",
                        "didn't like",
                        "didn't liked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is important that she ………………… what is happening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't realize",
                        "not realize",
                        "doesn't realize"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ……………….. Margaret – she already knows.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "needn't tell",
                        "needn't to tell"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. quick results when you start learning a new language.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Expect not",
                        "Not expect",
                        "Do not expect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is important ………………… waste your time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to not",
                        "not to",
                        "to don't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You seldom work on Sundays, ………………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do you",
                        "don't you",
                        "didn't you"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has few reasons for quitting, ………………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has he",
                        "hasn't he",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is little point in asking him, ……………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is there",
                        "isn't there"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn’t work here, ………………….?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does she",
                        "doesn't she",
                        "hasn't she"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}